Unless my people were freed
by Benjamin Franklin...
...and his five twin brothers,
you are wasting your time.
(Leonard(running in):)Hey. Sorry, I couldn't find a parking spot.
How are you doing?
(Howard:)Bad, very bad.
Really? You don't look
like you're swelling up.
We should pick up Benadryl
at the drugstore and go home.
- We can't go home.
- Why not?
Because... Phbbtt!
Brisket. Brisket.
(Howard:)- Water, need water.
- I'll be right back.
[CLEARING THROAT]
- Penny, listen, I've got a problem.
- Yeah, well, so do I.
- You gotta stall Leonard longer.
- I don't think I can.
(Penny:)You have to.
We all have to be there to yell "surprise."
(Howard:)You have to understand something.
We're in a hospital right now.
Why? Is Leonard okay?
(Howard:)Leonard's fine. I'm fine,
thanks for asking, by the way.